<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Accomplishments | 厦门大学智能医疗实验室</title>
    <link>/accomplishments/</link>
      <atom:link href="/accomplishments/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Accomplishments</description>
    <generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>/media/icon_hu0b7a4cb9992c9ac0e91bd28ffd38dd00_9727_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_2.png</url>
      <title>Accomplishments</title>
      <link>/accomplishments/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>俞容山论文</title>
      <link>/accomplishments/%E4%BF%9E%E5%AE%B9%E5%B1%B1%E8%AE%BA%E6%96%87/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/accomplishments/%E4%BF%9E%E5%AE%B9%E5%B1%B1%E8%AE%BA%E6%96%87/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;**代表性论文: **&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;R. Yu and W. Yang, “ScaleQC: A Scalable Lossy to Lossless Solution for NGS Data Compression,” Bioinformatics, 2020&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;M. Gao, M. Ling, X. Tang, S. Wang, X. Xiao, Y. Qiao, W. Yang, R. Yu, “Comparison of High-Throughput Single-Cell RNA Sequencing Data Processing Pipelines,” Brief in Bioinformatics, 2020&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;L. Wang, Y. Jiao, Y. Qiao, N. Zeng, R. Yu, “A novel approach combined transfer learning and deep learning to predict TMB from histology image,” Pattern Recognition Letters, 2020&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Y Lin, H Li, X Xiao, W Yang, R Yu, “DAISM-DNN: Highly accurate cell type proportion estimation with in silico data augmentation and deep neural networks,” bioRxiv, 2020&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;W. Yang, L. Huang, C. Shi, L. Wang, R. Yu, “UltraStrain: An NGS-Based Ultra Sensitive Strain Typing Method for Salmonella enterica,” Frontiers in Genetics, 2019&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;S. Wang, W, Yang, X. Zhang, R. Yu, “Performance Evaluation of IMP: A Rapid Secondary Analysis Pipeline for NGS Data,” IEEE International Conference on Bioinformatics and Biomedicine (BIBM) 2018&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;W. Yang, Y. Lin, S. Wu, R. Yu, “Improving Coding Efficiency of MPEG-G Standard Using Context-Based Arithmetic Coding,” IEEE International Conference on Bioinformatics and Biomedicine (BIBM) 2018&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;J. Hu, C. Si, M. Lind, R. Yu, “Preventing distribution grid congestion by integrating indirect control in a hierarchical electric vehicles’ management system,” IEEE Transactions on Transportation Electrification, Vol 2, No. 3, 2016&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;H. Shu, R. Yu, W. Jiang and W. Yang, &amp;ldquo;Efficient Implementation of $k$-Nearest Neighbor Classifier Using Vote Count Circuit,&amp;rdquo; IEEE Transactions on Circuit and System II, Vol. 61, No. 6, June 2014.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;R. Yu, H. Shu and W. Jiang, &amp;ldquo;Low Complexity Packet Scheduling Algorithms for Streaming Scalable Media Based on Time Utility Function,&amp;rdquo; IEEE Transactions on Multimedia, Vol. 16 , No. 8, pp. 2270 - 2280, Sep 2014.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;H. Shu, W. Yang, C. C. Chai and R. Yu, &amp;ldquo;Demand Response Based on Voluntary Time Dependent Pricing Scheme,&amp;rdquo; APSIPA Transactions on Signal and Information Processing, volume 3, 2014&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;R. Yu, Y. Song and M. Nambiar, &amp;ldquo;System Identification Using Prominent Subspace LMS,&amp;rdquo; Digital Signal Processing 27, 44-56, 2014&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;W. Yang, R. Yu, M. Nambiar, &amp;ldquo;Quantifying the Benefits to Consumers for Demand Response with a Statistical Elasticity Model&amp;rdquo;, IET Generation, Transmission &amp;amp; Distribution, Volume 8, Issue 3, p. 503 – 515, March 2014.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;H. Shu, R. Yu and H. Huang, &amp;ldquo;&amp;lsquo;Optimal Normalization of Prediction Residual for Predictive Coding with Random Access,&amp;rdquo; IET Signal Processing 09/2014 8(7):710-719&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;H. Huang, H. Shu and R. Yu, &amp;ldquo;Lossless Audio Compression in the New IEEE Standard for Advanced Audio Coding,&amp;rdquo; ICASSP 2014.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;W. Jiang, R. Yu, &amp;ldquo;High-Performance, Very Low Power Content-based Search Engine,&amp;rdquo; IEEE International Conference of Multimedia and Expo (ICME) 2013&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;R. Yu, &amp;ldquo;Speech enhancement based on soft audible noise masking and noise power estimation&amp;rdquo;, Speech Communication, 55 (2013), pp. 964-974, 2013.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;R. Yu, W. Yang, and S. Rahardja, “A statistical demand-price model with its application in optimal real-time price of electricity,” IEEE Transactions on Smart Grid, Vol. 3, No. 4, Dec 2012.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
